israelbiblecenter.com 2019-08-02

# Privacy Policy - ISRAEL BIBLE CENTER

This site (“ **Site** ” or **“www.IsraelStudyCenter.com”** ) is owned and operated by (“ **Owner** “).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting and using this Site, you acknowledge and agree that your use of our Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use](http://israelstudycenter.com/terms-of-use/).

**What Information Is Collected?**

At **“www.IsraelStudyCenter.com”** , we limit our collection of personal identifiable information of our users to the registration process which is done by the individual, the parent or the guardian of the child, who will be using the Site. We collect the following information from everyone upon registration to our Site: name, password, email address, name, phone number and date of birth of ( **“User Information** “). This information is collected so kids can participate in activities without giving unnecessary personal information and to receive personalized and appropriate learning experiences and materials.

**“www.IsraelStudyCenter.com”** does not condition a kid’s participation in any of our online activities on the disclosure of more information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity.

**Use of Information**

The User Information may be used by us solely for providing the services on **“www.IsraelStudyCenter.com”** , and for communications related to Owner services such as sending, newsletters, notices about new features, or other information of interest to you relating to **“www.IsraelStudyCenter.com”**.

The Site and the services therein are constantly evolving and changing in content and in features. User Information helps guide such changes and evolution. Accordingly, we may access non personally identifiable information such as your computer’s IP Address, and may gather aggregated information about yours and other users’ use of our Site, including, without limitation, the manner, consistency, duration and other information identifying the ways in which you and other users as whole use and access

**“www.IsraelStudyCenter.com”** and/or services therein. We also may aggregate various statistical and other data related to such use, including, without limitation, ascertaining aggregated usage, patterns and other behavioral information in order to expand and better develop our Site and services to enhance your experience. This information does not include individually identifiable personal information.

Owner will not distribute, sell or rent any User Information to other people or nonaffiliated companies (except for sale of **“www.IsraelStudyCenter.com”** as a whole to another entity, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process, where the acquirer shall undertake to materially comply with this Privacy Policy) except to enable the provision of services on our Site or when we have your permission to do so. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary, you acknowledge, consent, and agree that Owner may access, preserve, use, and disclose your User Information, if required to do so by law or in good faith believe that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) enforce the **“www.IsraelStudyCenter.com”**

Terms of Use (b) respond to your customer service requests; (c) comply with legal process; and/or (d) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Owner, its users, or the public.

**Cookies**

Owner places cookies on your computer to retain your individual preferences and improve your user experience with our site and services, as well as to tell us what features of our site, services or software are most popular. We do not store any personal identification information in cookies, nor do we use cookies to obtain any personal information from you. You can change the configuration of your browser in such a manner that you will not be able to receive any cookies during your use of Owner ‘s services, software or website. In that event, your access or use of certain parts of our site, software or services, may be restricted.

**For Kids**

Remember to be smart online. Do not give out your full name, e-mail address, home address, telephone number or any other personal information that would enable someone to contact you either online or offline, without first asking your parent or guardian for permission.

Sometimes on our **“www.IsraelStudyCenter.com”** site we will ask you for your first name and e-mail address along with your parents’ e-mail address. We do this so that we can contact your parents to let them know that you have communicated with us, and that we have collected this information from you.

**Security**

Owner takes commercially reasonable organizational and technical steps to protect the privacy of your personal identifiable information. Owner will make best efforts to ensure that your information will be accessible only by authorized employees of Owner who need to have access to this information in order to provide you with the services on **“www.IsraelStudyCenter.com”**. However, you should be aware that there is no data that is transmitted over the Internet that can be guaranteed 100% secure in transmission or safe from theft or illegal capture, and therefore we do not guarantee absolute resistance from unauthorized access.

**Consent to Transfer**

Please be aware that information we collect may be transferred to and processed in another country. By using the Site, or providing us with any information, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, transfer, processing and storage of your information in the country of our choosing, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside and/or are a citizen.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Owner may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a prominent notice on our website. In addition, the date at the top of this Privacy Policy will indicate when this policy has most recently been revised; we encourage you to periodically revisit this Privacy Policy to ensure that you are familiar with the current version.

**Your continued use of the Owner website, after any change to the policy constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.**

**Questions / Concerns?**

**YOUR COMMENTS AND CONCERNS**

This website is operated by Owner.  
All notices of copyright infringement claims should be sent to [info@IsraelBibleCenter.com](mailto:info@IsraelBibleCenter.com) and ccied to [info@israelstudycenter.com](mailto:info@israelstudycenter.com). All other feedback, comments, requests for technical support and other communications relating to the Website should be directed to: [info@IsraelBibleCenter.com](mailto:info@IsraelBibleCenter.com)
